[
	{
		"id": 1,
		"type": "question",
		"game": "lba1",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"author": "kit",
		"question": "How many elves are in The Elves Club?",
		"answer": "4 - Joe, Raymond, one unnamed elf, and Twinsen (introduced as the 4th member)"
	},
	{
		"id": 2,
		"type": "question",
		"game": "lba1",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"author": "Phreak",
		"question": "Which country were the developers of LBA from?",
		"answer": "France"
	},
	{
		"id": 3,
		"type": "question",
		"game": "lba1",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"author": "Phreak",
		"question": "What is the name of Twinsen's friend who gets arrested?",
		"answer": "Zoé"
	},
	{
		"id": 4,
		"type": "question",
		"game": "lba2",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"author": "Phreak",
		"question": "Skeletons bow to nitro meca penguins? (True or False)",
		"answer": "True"
	},
	{
		"id": 5,
		"type": "question",
		"game": "lba2",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"author": "kit",
		"question": "Which item grants Twinsen the second level of magic (green ball)?",
		"answer": "Wizard's Diploma"
	},
	{
		"id": 6,
		"type": "question",
		"game": "lba2",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"author": "kit",
		"question": "What is the 4th level of magic called?",
		"answer": "Fireball"
	},
	{
		"id": 7,
		"type": "question",
		"game": "lba1",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"author": "kit",
		"question": "Which facility is located on Brundle Island?",
		"answer": "Teleportation Center"
	},
	{
		"id": 8,
		"type": "question",
		"game": "lba1",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"author": "kit",
		"question": "What is the secret underground town called located on Tipett Island?",
		"answer": "Funky-Town"
	},
	{
		"id": 9,
		"type": "question",
		"game": "lba2",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"author": "kit",
		"question": "Who is the mother of the umbrella thief?",
		"answer": "Mrs Brune - she works at the Citadel Island Ferry ticket office and also has another son who attends the school."
	},
	{
		"id": 10,
		"type": "question",
		"game": "lba2",
		"difficulty": "hard",
		"author": "kit",
		"question": "In Zeelich lore, what was the original name of the one known as Dark Monk?",
		"answer": "Kard N’kom"
	},
	{
		"id": 11,
		"type": "question",
		"game": "lba2",
		"difficulty": "medium",
		"author": "kit",
		"question": "Which item does Twinsen need to collect to finish the Lightning Potion?",
		"answer": "Pearl of Incandescence"
	},
	{
		"id": 12,
		"type": "question",
		"game": "lba2",
		"difficulty": "easy",
		"author": "kit",
		"question": "What does the lighthouse keeper say the Tralü will turn him into?",
		"answer": "rabbibunny-melba"
	}
]
